TRISHIA ANN CABUANG



I'm a web developer and designer who specializes in creating and maintaining websites, particularly those built with CMS. I am also an SEO Specialist with proven results. I have four years of work experience in both of these fields.

EXPERIENCE

CMS Website Developer & Designer Local Digital Experts | June 2018 - August 2022 (Working Student / Part-Time)

- Mostly WordPress, Weebly, & ClickFunnels.
- Domain registration and hosting.
- Designing and building the website front-end.
- Creating the website architecture.
- Meeting with clients to discuss website design and function.
- Web maintenance and blog updates.

SEO Specialist

Local Digital Experts | June 2018 - August 2022 (Working Student / Part-Time)

- Create optimization strategies to boost the company's search engine rankings.
- Off-page and On-page optimization.
- Daily backlinking / link-building.
- Investigate SEO keywords for use on the company's website and marketing materials.

Social Media Manager

Local Digital Experts | June 2018 - August 2022 (Working Student / Part-Time)

- Developing & Planning Social Media Campaigns.
- Coming up with engaging material or having it created.
- Deploy ads.
- Posting content across social media accounts.
- Running campaign analysis

BaybaySalin

Thesis Project | November 2021 - March 2022

- BaybaySalin: A Baybayin Script recognition and conversion into Filipino text using SurfCNN algorithm.
- HTML, CSS & Python (plus flask) were also used.
- Deployed through Ngrok.

CONTACT

- +63 995 453 2395
- trishiacabuang.work@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/trishia-ann-cabuang/
- github.com/devtagcabuang

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Polytechnic University of the Philippines Main Campus

2018 - September 2022 (Expected)

Relevant Coursework:

- Design & conduct experiments on computer systems.
- Identify, formulate, and solve complex
- problems.
- Project Management & Systems Thinking.
- Research & Planning

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript

Content Management System

- WordPress
- Weebly
- Cloudflare
- ClickFunnels

Tools / Technologies

- Git
- Linux Operating System
- Windows Operating System

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Diligent
- Fast Learner
- Self-motivated
- Organized
- Ability to work in a team or independently.
- Adaptability